{
    "subject": "resource/WTYS_(AM)",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "WTYS (1340 AM) is a radio station broadcasting a bluegrass and country music format. Licensed to Marianna, Florida, USA.  The station is currently owned by James L. Adams, Jr.",
    "human_readable": "The comment about WTYS (AM) states that it's a radio station broadcasting a bluegrass and country music format, licensed to Marianna, Florida, USA, and currently owned by James L. Adams, Jr.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8989747762680054,
            "question": "Is WTYS (AM) a radio station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8463402390480042,
            "question": "Who currently owns WTYS (AM)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8444843888282776,
            "question": "Where is WTYS (AM) licensed to broadcast from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.816403329372406,
            "question": "Name the owner of WTYS (AM)."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7175785303115845,
            "question": "What genres of music does WTYS (AM) broadcast?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7098025679588318,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where WTYS (AM) is licensed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6597339510917664,
            "question": "What type of music format does WTYS (AM) feature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6107775568962097,
            "question": "Where can you listen to WTYS (AM)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5369595885276794,
            "question": "In what state is Marianna located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3194257616996765,
            "question": "What is the call sign of the radio station?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about WTYS (AM) states that it's a radio station broadcasting a bluegrass and country music format, licensed to Marianna, Florida, USA, and currently owned by James L. Adams, Jr.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3948_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what state is Marianna located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3948_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you listen to WTYS (AM)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3948_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of music format does WTYS (AM) feature?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3948_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3948_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3948_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3948_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3948_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3948_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3948_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3948_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3948_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3948_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3948_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context information confirms the details about WTYS (AM) being a radio station broadcasting a bluegrass and country music format, licensed to Marianna, Florida, USA, and currently owned by James L. Adams, Jr. This aligns with the statement in the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}